N.C.Mohit

Hyderabad, Telangana 7780341997 n.mohit18@st.niituniversity.in

I'm a programming enthusiast interested in learning and applying upcoming new technologies, proficient in debugging, optimization and integration of software. Currently pursuing studies in the field of Artificial Intelligence and looking forward to expand my skill set and gain real-world experience

WORK EXPERIENCE

TCO, NIIT UNIVERSITY

Neemrana

Feb 2020 – May 2020

PHP Backend Developer Internship

- Fixing bugs and optimizing backend systems.
- Fixing compatibility issues while transferring the entire system to an optimized environment.
- Learned new tools to integrate into the current working system.

SHIVEDIC TECHNOLOGIES

Online

PHP Backend Developer Internship

July 2019 – August 2019

- Linking databases to the frontend.
- Designing Scripts to send queries to the backend database.
- Designing server side logic for authentication.
- Securing server against XSS using sanitization.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

GAIT Recognition

Mar 2021 – *May* 2021

 A novel approach to use Image moments as a unique feature for detecting GAIT signatures.

Spatial Network A-Star Clustering

Mar 2021 – May 2021

• A system that clusters Californian road network dataset, and uses it as a heuristic for calculating shortest path between two nodes using a star algorithm.

Video Frame Interpolation using ML

Mar 2021 – May 2021

• A technique to synthesize frames between two frames by isolating and predicting positions of objects and interpolating, increasing fps of video.

PocketWork - A local recruitment website

Feb 2021 – May 2021

• A website for local job posting and recruitment. Made using TailWindCSS, Python-Flask, Python-SQLAlchemy

EDUCATION

National Institute of Information and Technology UNIVERSITY

Neemrana

B. Tech Computer Science and Technology

Jul 2018 - Present

CGPA: 8.87 / 10 (Semester-6)

Narayana Jr College

Hvderabad

Senior Secondary Education

Jul 2016 - Jul 2018

GPA: 926 / 1000

Linkedin: N.C Mohit | LinkedIn Github: NCMohit